7. Internet Gossip Websites. Gossip has existed as long as humans have
lived together. We have always gossiped about our friends and family, but we will even sometimes
gossip about people we have never met. Recently, the Internet has become a home for thousands
of celebrity gossip websites, websites that constantly update readers about the actions
of their favorite, or least favorite, celebrities. Through these websites, rumors can be spread
to millions of people almost instantly. Often, this gossip is unkind. Often, it can also
be untrue. Whether it's true or not, information that
spreads so far and so fast can be very damaging to a celebrity's career. Because of this,
many celebrities hate these websites. They say the websites invade their privacy. Some
celebrities have sued the websites or writers of the sites. Many of these lawsuits have
been successful, meaning the websites have been forced to correct false stories or pay
money to celebrities. But other celebrities encourage gossip websites. They believe all
publicity is good publicity. Some of them even work with the paparazzi, photographers
who follow celebrities, to make sure the paparazzi will know where they are and take pictures
of them. They feel they must remain in the public eye in order to remain popular. In
this way, some celebrities and gossip websites form a cycle. The celebrities feed the paparazzi
by posing for photos. Then, the paparazzi feed the photos to gossip websites, and the
gossip websites feed the photos to consumers. Consumers see the photos and then want even
more information about the celebrities. This, of course, means the celebrities will continue
to pose, and the paparazzi will continue to take photos. But in the end, it isn't the
paparazzi or celebrities who are the reason for these websites. We average human beings
and our hunger for gossip are the reason these websites still exist.